data-flair.training 2019-05-27

# Privacy Policy Overview - DataFlair

### Privacy Policy Overview

User privacy is very important for Data-flair.training and takes it seriously and is committed to protect your privacy as a user of our website. We have made all possible efforts to ensure your information is secure. All information collected, what we do with it, and what you can do about it is covered in this privacy policy. You can use this information to decide about your privacy.

#### About us and the website

Data-flair.training provides online training, consulting services, consultancy and implementation for big data, Hadoop ecosystem, Apache Spark, Scala, Storm, Core Java, business Intelligence, Kafka, HBase, cloud technologies and other niche technologies. We help candidates in carving their career.

#### Data-flair Information Practices

DataFlair tries to ensure about the Accuracy of the information and details on the website; the Site content may change from time to time. We will not be responsible for any damages arising due to the usage of the information on this server.  
Information collected by us – We give you 100% assurance that we will not provide any of your information that is available with us to any another company or person without your permission. We keep your information 100% safe and secure and will never sell, exchange or disclose to any third party for marketing purposes. Website browsing does not need any registration by user. To access our discussion forum, we may collect and store the information that you share with us. We do not share your personal information with any third party. Email databases, private public organization or other bodies are not being used by us to collect data about our visitors.  
Information collected from you can be used by us to contact you to get feedback, to inform you about new products or provide support on your issues.  
To purchase our online products, you need to do online payment for which you will be required to share your personal information such as name, e-mail address, telephone number, address(s) details with us. During this program, your contact information is stored in our registration systems. We do not store your PayPal and PayU information in our system as it is processed by our payment gateway which uses Secure Encryption Technology (SSL). PayPal (outside India) and PayU (within India) are our payment processing partners.

#### External Links

It may happen that our website may contain links to other sites which includes third party websites or resources. Users must be careful and we are not responsible for the information practices and privacy policies of third party websites. Privacy policies of third party websites must be carefully read by Users as every website has different terms and policies.

#### Course Curriculum

Course content for all the study programs, online training, it is provided for education and guidance only. We regularly review The course content and it is subjected to change without notice.

#### Access to training material of DataFlair

Sharing of Data-flair training materials and site credentials to your friends, any family members, guardians or any colleagues is strictly prohibited and can have legal implications. If anyone found sharing these, we will disable permanently his/her account and he/she will be un-enrolled from the course automatically without giving any warning.

#### Copyright information

All the contents present on website of data-flair.training can be used for personal use but a written permission must be obtained. DataFlair holds the copyright to all the materials and contents that are available on this website, unless otherwise indicated. For using contents or materials present on this site, a written permission must be obtained from the copyright holder for any use of this material other than for purposes permitted by law.

#### Personal Information Policy

Sharing your personal information  
Users who purchase any of the courses available on Data-flair may be asked for testimonial regarding their experience in learning that course and it will be displayed on our website along with photos and videos, and also may be shared on our social media channels like Linkedin, Facebook, Google+, Twitter, YouTube or Flickr or can email them to our customers. Users must be aware that their publicly identifiable details could be used to send promotional, unsolicited messages. DataFlair is not responsible for any such personal information that users have chosen to display. If any user does not want his picture testimonials to be displayed, he/she can write a mail to info@data-flair.training informing the same.

#### Correcting Personal Information

If user finds that his information we are holding is incorrect or not complete, he can send us a mail with the correct details at info@data-flair.training.

#### Changes to Privacy Policy

The privacy policy terms are subject to change from time to time and we hold the right to change the terms of this privacy policy at any time. So users are strongly recommended to periodically review this Privacy Policy so that they are aware about how we are protecting the personal information of the users. Your continued use of this Site means that you agree to this Privacy Policy or any changes being made in it.

#### Removing Personal Information

If any user would like to remove his account, he can write as mail at info@data-flair.training mentioning the same.

#### Privacy Policy Queries

If any user has any query regarding Data-flair Privacy Policy, they can write to info@data-flair.training
